http://tuff-as-nuts.com/pages/privacy-policy

Home About NutshellHow to Buy a NutshellVertical NutshellsHorizontal NutshellsNutshells for Accessorry Cases OtterBox Apple iPhone X in Otterbox SymmetryApple iPhone X in Otterbox Strada FolioApple iPhone X in Otterbox CommuterSamsung Galaxy S4 in Otterbox DefenderApple iPhone 6 / 6s / 7 / 8 in Otterbox SymmetryApple iPhone 6 / 6s / 7 / 8 in Otterbox DefenderApple iPhone 6 / 6s / 7 / 8 in Otterbox DefenderLifeProof Apple iPhone X in Lifeproof Crystal ProApple iPhone 6 / 6s / 7 / 8 in Lifeproof Case2 Year WarrantyReturns & RefundsShippingTerms of TradeContactPrivacyGifts Give a Nutshell Gift CardLeather CareNutshell Options Holsters by SizeHorizontal HolstersSelect Your ColorBelt Clip or Belt Loop?Add a Pocket or Penloop?About NutshellHolsters for Smartphones A-L Apple iPhone 12 iPhone 12 ProiPhone 12 Pro MaxiPhone 12 MiniiPhone SE (2020)iPhone 11iPhone 11 ProiPhone 11 Pro MaxiPhone Xs Max Accessory Covers for Apple iPhone Xs-MaxiPhone XRiPhone Xs Accessory Covers for Apple iPhone XsApple iPhone Xs with slim leather or silicone coveriPhone X Apple iPhone x with Leather or Silicone coverAccessory Covers for Apple iPhone XiPhone 8 PlusiPhone 8iPhone 7 PlusiPhone 7 iPhone 7 in Lifeproof CaseiPhone 7 in Speck MightyshelliPhone 7 in Lifeproof CaseiPhone 6 iPhone 6 in Lifeproof CaseiPhone 6 in Otterbox CommuteriPhone 6 in Speck MightyshelliPhone 6sAlcatel Pop 4 PlusAlcatel 10.16GFierce XLFlash 2Go PlayIdol 3CIdol 4Blackberry KEY2KEY2 LEKEYoneMotionPrivDTEK60DTEK50PassportBLU BLU Dash XBLU Grand 5.5 HDBLU Neo X MiniBLU Studio G2BLU Studio M LTEFigo FiGO Atrium\FiGO DuosFiGO EpicGoogle Pixel 4APixel 3 XLPixel 3Pixel 2 XLPixel 2Pixel XLPixelHonor Honor 10iHP Elite x3Slate 6 VoiceTab IIHTC HTC U11HTC U11 lifeHTC 10HTC 10 LifestyleOne S9Huawei Mate 40 Mate 40 ProMate 40 Pro+Mate 40 RS Porsche DesignEnjoy 10 PlusP30P30 ProP30 LiteMate 20 ProMate 20 XMate 20 liteHonor 8XP20P20 ProP20 LiteP10P9 PlusG7 PlusMate 10 LiteKarbonn A6 TurboAura PowerFashion EyeKyocera DuraForce ProBrigadierHydro ReachHydro ViewLavaLG G8X ThinQ with 2 screensG8 ThinQLG Q Stylo 4LG V35 THINQLG Q7LG Q6LG X ventureLenovo S5 ProHolsters for Smartphones M-Z Meizu Meizu Pro 6Motorola Motorola Edge PlusMoto Z PlayMoto G4 PlusDroid Turbo 2Microsoft Surface DuoLumia 650Lumia 950NokiaNubiaOnePlus OnePlus NordOnePlus 6TOnePlus 6OnePlus 5OnePlus 3Oppo A5s (AX5s)Joy 3R5sA33A37F1F1 PlusR7 PlusR7sR9 PlusR9s PlusRealme Narzo 20 ProSonim XP7 Custom HolsterXP5Samsung Galaxy Fold2Galaxy FoldGalaxy Note20 Ultra 5GGalaxy A71Galaxy S20 Galaxy S20+S20 ULTRAGalaxy A51Note 10+Note 10+ 5GNote 10 5GGalaxy A40Galaxy S10Galaxy S10+Galaxy S9Galaxy S9+Galaxy Note 9Galaxy Note 8Galaxy S8 PlusGalaxy A6Galaxy S8S7 EdgeGalaxy S7Galaxy Note 5Sharp Aquos R2Vodafone Smart N8Smart prime 7Smart ultra 7Smart V8SonyVertu Vertu Signature Touch (2015)Vertu AsterVertu Signature TouchVivo NEXX27Xiaomi Redmi Note 7 ProMi Mix 3Xiaomi Mi 4cXiaomi Mi 4sXiaomi Mi 5Xiaomi Mi 5sXiaomi Mi A1Xiaomi Mi A2Xiaomi Mi MaxXiaomi Poco M3Xiaomi Redmi 3 ProXiaomi Redmi 3s PrimeXiaomi Redmi 3xXiaomi Redmi 4Xiaomi Redmi 4aXiaomi Redmi Note 9 ProXOLOZTE Blade Max 2sMedical Belt Cases Insulin Pumps & Meters Accu-chek Accu-Chek Aviva ConnectAccu-Chek MobileAccu-Chek NanoAccu-Chek Spirit MonitorAnimas Animas Vibe MonitorMedtronic MiniMed 530GMiniMed Paradigm RevelMedtronic GuardianMedtronic Paradigm 515Medtronic Paradigm 722/722KMedtronic Paradigm 723/723KNeurostimulators Ultima 5 Digital TENS unitStuff Nutshell BlogTight Nutshell? Try this. It works.Old Nutshells Never Die. Customer photos.
Search
Home
Holsters
Horizontal Holsters
Apple iPhone
Holsters for Samsung Smartphones
Sonim XP7
Leather Care
PRIVACY STATEMENT
SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address. When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates. SECTION 2 - CONSENTHow do you get my consent?When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no. How do I withdraw my consent?If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at:
sales@nutshell.co.nz
or by postal mail at:Nutshell Corporation LimitedAttention: Privacy Compliance OfficerPO Box 99135NewmarketAuckland 1149New Zealand
SECTION 3 - DISCLOSUREWe may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service. SECTION 4 - SHOPIFYOur store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that enables us to sell our products and services to you. Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.Payment:If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify’s Terms of Service here or Privacy Statement here.SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICESIn general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.  However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.  In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.
Google Opt-Out PolicyLinksWhen you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.
SECTION 6 - SECURITYTo protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption.  Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.SECTION 7 - COOKIES Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not. _session_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc). _shopify_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits _shopify_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart. _secure_session_id, unique token, sessional storefront_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.SECTION 8 - AGE OF CONSENT By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your country, state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your country, state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.SECTION 9 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYWe reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATIONIf you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at:
sales@nutshell.co.nz
or by postal mail at:Nutshell Corporation LimitedAttention: Privacy Compliance Officer PO Box 99135 Newmarket Auckland 1149 New Zealand
Back to the top
